CONTACT

- (857) 320-8390
- ⋈ leo.thibaudat@gmail.com
- ↑ 15 Raymond Ave
 Somerville, MA

MEDIAS

- in linkedin.com/in/leothibaudat
- ★ github.com/thibaudatl

PROFILE

I am a 27 years old green card holder French software engineer living in Somerville, MA. I spend some of my spare time working on side projects with a Raspberry PI, building connected devices. I enjoy working with Javascript frameworks like Vue.JS and I would like to learn more about ReactJS. I also love to cook and I spend a fair amont of time in the kitchen trying to make very tasty, sometimes healthy, dishes.

LANGUAGES

French
English
German

MY IDEAL JOB

I would be part of a small to medium size team with knowlegeable, proactive and funny teammates, developing a web or mobile (PWA, react-native, vue-native) application. We would have some time to contribute to open-source projects, or share some of our work with the community and coworkers.

The company would have a healthy, supportive and sharing oriented work culture.

LEO THIBAUDAT

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCES

Bubbleflat - Toulouse, France

Lead developer

Apr 2017- present

Leading a team of 3 and developing a web marketplace focused on helping people to find roommates and housing. The application has helped over 20k users in France and Europe. We worked with Php Laravel, Vue.js, AWS EC2 & Mysql to develop the whole front-end from scratch. Participated in CES 2018 in Las Vegas, NV.

Zeillo - Toulouse, France

Co-Founder & Developer

Jan 2017 - present

As a personal side project, I designed, developed and deployed an offline, and later online, white labeled platform for restaurants and bars to manage their digital menu displays. Several bars use my device in Toulouse, France. Work with Raspberry PI, Laravel & Git.

Car360 inc.- Atlanta, GA

Full-stack web developer (Intern)

Jan 2016 - Sept 2016

Lead a team of 3 people to design, develop and maintain a client facing admin panel platform for the Car360 application. Projects with Javascript, Php & Wordpress for the startup.

INRA - Toulouse. France

Full-stack web developer (Intern)

Jul 2015- Sept 2015

Created a web application conntected to a NoSQL Couchdb database to centralize data for metagenomics research. Studied users' needs and developed the app in Python and the framework Pyramid.

EDUCATION

EIGSI Engineering school - La Rochelle, France

Master's Degree - Networks & programming

Sept 2011 - Dec 2016

Classes: Pinciples of Networks, OSs, Mobile App, OOP, System security, Web principles.

Olin College Of Engineering - Needham, MA

Semester abroad - Design & development

Sept 2014 - Dec 2014

Classes: Human Factor in Interface design, Entrepreneurship, Software Design.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front











Back







Webpack, real time notifications

REST API, Redis Caching, Nginx